Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Chefs
  - Pelichero, Richard, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Pellegrini, Luciano, undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Pellegrino, Cala (Rao's), 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Pellegrino, Stuart, 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Pelletier, Claude, 2002-2006 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Penati, Paolo, Jan. 7, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Pence, Caprial, 1987-2003 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Penna, Giorgio, Jan. 22, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Penner, Kevin, 1996-2001 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Pentecost, Randall, 1990-1997; various (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Pepin, Jacques (1 of 2), 1996-1997; various (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Pepin, Jacques, undated (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Per Mio Figlio, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Pereira, Cliff, May 30, 1994; March 11, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Perello, Melissa, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Perez, Greg, January 1994 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Perez, Sara, April 6, 2007; various (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Perez, Justin, 2000-2005 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Perez, Mario, 2001-2003 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Perini, Tom, 1990-2002 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Perkins, Timothy, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Pernetti, Steve, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Perno, Jonathan, 1998-2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Pernot, Guillermo, 1996-2003 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Perotti, Roberto, March 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Perrazzo, Ralph, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Perrier Group, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Perrier, Frederick, 1990-1998 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Perrier, Georges, 1991-1997 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Perrone, Peter, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Perroti, Ralph, May 22, 1992; various (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Perry Lang, Adam, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Perry, Kathleen, Feb. 1, 1993; various (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Perry, Neil, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Perry, Richard, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Perticone, Giovanni, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Petersen, Kjeld, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Peterson, Harlan, 1985-1996 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Peterson, Holly, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Peterson, James, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Peterson, Michael, 1993-2000 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Peterson, Steven, undated (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Petiteau, Pascal, 1994-2004 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Petrakos, Takis, undated (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Pezzilli, Vincenzo, 1999-2003 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Pfeifer, Horst, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Pfeiffer, Jacquy, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Phan, Charles, 1995-2005 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Philip, Sinclair, 1984-1994 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Philip, Scott, July 13, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Philips, Melicia, May 11, 1993; various (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Picard, Justin, April 24, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Piccarello, Frederick/French Roast, undated (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Picciotto, Rafael, undated (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Piccolotto, Renato, June 22, 1998; various (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Picker, Steven, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Pickus, Karen, undated (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Picolo, Gregory, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Picone, Gennaro, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Picone, Mark, 1999-2003 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Pierce, Stacie, undated (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Pierola, Jeannie, undated (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Pierre-Jerome, Patrick Yves, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Pieton, Michel, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Pietromonaco, Richard, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Piggott, Linda, 1985-1994 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Pigozzi, Roger, 1923; 1993-1998 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Pinato, Giovanni, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Pinckney, David, 1985-1996 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Pinhao, Luiza, January 16, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Pino, Anthony David, 2002-2004 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Pinsuvana, Malulee, 1986-1999 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Pintabona, Don, undated (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Piper, Odessa, 1993-2001 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Piqueras, Emmanuel, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Piscareta, Jerry, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Pisaniello, Antonio, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Pisano, Walter, 1994-1998 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Piscopo, Paul, undated (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Pitts, Alex, 1999-2000; various (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Piuggi, Lou, 1995-2000 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Pivar, John, 2000-2003 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - Platt, Peter, 1992-2005 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Pleau, Clifford, 2001-2005 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Plender, Walter, 1991-2001 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Plugra, 1993-1996 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Plunton, Jacky, 1992-1994 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - Plympton, Jo Ann, 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - Poidevin, Marc, Sept. 1994, Nov. 2003; various (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - Poirier, William, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - Polatkesen, Zeki, 1994-1997 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Polegri, Lorenzo, 1999-2007 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Polyn, Brian, 1987-1993 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Poli, Ryan, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Poliquin, Benoit, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 5a)
  - Poll, William, 1942, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5b)
  - Pollack, Ronald, 1996-2006 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Pollinger, Ben, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Polosa, Vito, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Ponsaty, Patrick, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Ponsford, Craig, March 7, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Ponte, Guida, 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Pontes, Julius, Oct. 19, 2001; various (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Ponzek, Debra, 1988-2003 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Poo, Porcus, 1991, various (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Pooler, Keith, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Poon, Joseph, 1999-2005 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Poor, Brian, 1993-1995 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Pope, Monica, 1994-2003 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Popovic, Scott, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Porceddu, Marco, undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Portale, Alfred, 1992-2004 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Portay, Sylvain, 1992-2002 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Porteus, James, February 1997 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Poses, Steve, March 28, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Potanovich, Jason, 2002-2006 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Poteaux, Christophe, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Potenza, Walter, 1988-2006 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Pothier, Maureen, March 19, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Potovsky, Steve, undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Pouillon, Nora, 1994-1996 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Poulain, Laurent, Oct. 2000; various (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Pounding, Rob, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Pourcel, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Poursohi, Fazol ("Faz"), 1987-1993 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Poussot, Herve, undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Powell, Alex, April 17, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Power, Thomas, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Prado, Toribio, 1987-1999 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Prasad, Romesh, undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Prather, Jeff, undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Pratt, Adrian, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Pratt, Jonathan, undated (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Prentice, Matthew, Jan. 15, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Presilla, Maricel, 1992-2004 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Previti, Drew, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Price, Mike, undated (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Price, Robert, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Privitera, Philip, April 8, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Prosperi, Alessandro, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Prosperi, Bernie, undated (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Prosperi, Chris, 1990-2002 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Prudhomme, Paul, 1989-1995 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Prunty, William, January 1996 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Pryor, Peter, 1996-1998 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Psaltis, Doug, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Psilakis, Michael, 2004-2006 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Publicker, Bette, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Pucci, Ruggerio, March 15, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Puck, Wolfgang, 1989-2008 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - Pulin, Marta, 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Pulito, Leonardo, 1987-1999 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Pulix, Carlo, Nov. 26, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Pulla, Jorge ("Giorgio"), 1997 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Pulomena, Kenneth, June 17, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Purdy, Mark, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Purnomo, Donna J., undated (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Purnomo, Widgiono, 1986-2001 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Purvis, Simon, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Putnam, Stephen, 1997-2001 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Pyles, Stephan, 1987-2001 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Quadalti, Giancarlo, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Quagliarella, Andrea, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Qualin, Jacques, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Quatrano, Anne, 1993-2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Quattara, Morou, 1992-1999 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Quay, Dominique, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Queen, Patty, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Quingerez, Tony, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Quinn, Timothy, 1998-2005 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Quintana, Patrick, 1982-2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Quinones, Ernie, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Quitney, Mark, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Quito, Claudio, 2002-2007 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Quintana, Joseph, Nov. 24, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Rabin, Robert ("Nitzi"), 1990-1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Rachou, Jean-Jacques, 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Racicot, Deborah, Dec. 4, 2001; various (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rafala, Paul, Nov. 4, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Raggiri, Anthony, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Raider, Jeff, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Raij, Alexandra and Eder Montero, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Rainwater Restaurant, March 17, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Rajender, Rana, Jan. 17, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Rajkovic, Rosa, April 11, 1992; various (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Ramella, Felice, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Ramirez, Mario, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Ramirez, Nestor, 1992-2002 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Ramos, Fred, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Ramos, Erwin, 2003-2006 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Ramos, Jules, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Ramouneda, Bernard, Dec. 1999 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Ramsay, Gordon, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Ramseyer, Charles, 1996-2001 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Rana, Rajender, Apr. 25, 2005; various (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Randall, Joseph, May 1993, Feb. 1995 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Rangel, David, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Randazzo, Frank, 1999-2006 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Ranieri, Maria, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Rapp, Tom and Jonathan, 1993-1995 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Rappaport, Andrea, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Rashid, Justin, March 29, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Rassinoux, Christian, Aug. 27, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Rathbone, Dounia, 1980-1992 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Rathbun, Kevin, 1993-2006 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Rathburn, Kent, undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Rautureau, Thierry, 1988-2000 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Ravago, Miguel, 1995-2002 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Rayment, Richard, 1995-2000 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Raymer, David, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Raz, Nitzan, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Realmuto, Joseph, Nov. 14, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Reardon, David, 1997-2003 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Reardon, Jeremiah, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Reaux, James, 1999-2003 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Reda, John Michael, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Reda, Sam, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Reddington, Richard, 2002-2006 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Redelsperger, Alain, 1995-1998 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Rezic, Dino, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Reed, Alvin, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Rees, John, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Rees, Rob, 2006-2007 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Regis, Susan, February 1995; various (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Reid, Everett G. III, Jan. 31, 1997; various (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Reidt, Michael, 1999-2005 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Reilly, Daniel, 2000-2002 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Reilly, John, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Reilly, Kevin, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Reinbold, Guy, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Reininger, Philippe, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Reis, George, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Reis, Leslee, March 29, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Renard, Andre, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Renaud, Cyril, 1996-2003 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Renggli, Seppi, 1989-1994 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Renkl, Jeffrey, 1997;various (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Rennie, Keith, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Renshaw, Rodney, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Resch, Pamela R., 1991-1996 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Reschreiter, Oliver, Sept. 11, 2005; various (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Respinto, Giani, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Restrepo, Paul, Feb. 26, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Reuge, Guy, 1984-2003 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Revsin, Leslie, 1988-1994 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Reymond, Michel, 1988-1994 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Reynaud, Philippe Paul, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Reynolds, Lindsey, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Reynolds, Robert, 1992-1999 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Reynoso, David, 1992-1999 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Rhodes, Frank, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Ribera, Maxime, 1985-1996 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Ricchi, Francesco, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Riccioletti, Stefano, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Rice, Kevin, undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Rich, Evan, undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Richard, Michel, 1990-2004 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Richards, Todd, Nov. 29, 2006; various (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Richardson, Andrew, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Richardson, Ferrier, Nov. 22, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Richardson, Howard, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Richter, Mary, 1988-1997 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Riebel, Jack, undated (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Riezenman, Bruce, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Rigo, Pascal, 1997-2004 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Riley, Casey, 1993-2005 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Riley, Michael, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Rindge, John, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Riordin, Kevin, 1996-2002 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Riordin, Michael, undated (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Rios, Martin, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Ripert, Eric, 1986-2005 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Ritter, Tracy, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Riva, Della, Dec. 1992 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Rivers, Johnn, March 6, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Rivetti, Giorgio, undated (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Rizzuto, Robert, Sept. 2002; various (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Robert, Jacky and Andree, 1990-2007 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Roberts, Michael, 1988-1999 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Robertson, Antonia "Toni", 1990-2005 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Robertson, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Robin, Lionel, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Robins, David, March 23, 1994; July 28, 2003; various (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Robins, Gary, 1992-2004 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Robinson, George, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Robinson, Jason, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Robinson, Thomas, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Robinson, Lawrence, 2000-2007 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Robledo-Richards, Luis, Jan. 2004 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Robuchon, Joel, Dec. 1993; April 15, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Robusti, Gino, Sept. 28, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Rocca, Ella, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Rocchi, Girogio, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Rochat, Andre, 1998-2005 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Rockenwagner, Hans, 1991-2001 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Rodgers, Judy, 1989-1994 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Rodriguez, Douglas, 1994-2006 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Rodriguez, Juan Carlos, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Rodriguez, Mark, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Rodriguez, Pilar, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Roen, Megan, undated (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Rogers, Jason, May 4, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Rogers, John Kelly, 1994-2003 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Rogers, Todd, May 1, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Rojas, Alejandro, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Rojas,-Lombardi, Felipe, 1983-1992 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Rokh, Lala, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - Romano, Joe and Megan, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Romano, Michael, 1991-2005 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Romano, Rosario, 1990-2000 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Romeo, Stephen, June 20, 1995; various (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Romero, Anibal, undated (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Rondelli, Alain, 1990-1996 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Ronis, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Rork, Michael, 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - Rosa, Francisco, 2000-2005 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Rose, Anthony, Jan. 12, 2004; various (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - Rose, Jill, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - Rose, Peter, Sept. 5, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - Rosen, Ilene, May 18, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - Rosen, Steve, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 94)
  - Rosenbaum, Ron, undated (Box 40, Folder 95)
  - Rosenthal, Mitchell and Steven, 1995-1999 (Box 40, Folder 96)
  - Rosenzweig, Anne, 1993-2001 (Box 40, Folder 97)
  - Ross, Michael, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 98)
  - Ross, Ron, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 99)
  - Ross, Rosa, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 100)
  - Rossi, Christopher, 1999-2004 (Box 40, Folder 101)
  - Rossman, Arnold, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 102)
  - Rossmann, Fabrice, Oct. 28, 2002; various (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Rosso, Jason, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Rostang, Michel, 1985-2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Roth, Kevin, Oct. 27, 1999; various (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Rouband, Yves, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Rouissiya, Mustapha, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Roush, Jeremy, Feb. 11, 2002; various (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Roussel, Devlin, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Roussel, Philippe, 1999-2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Routh, Dorothy, March 1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Rovito, Teresa, 1991-2001 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Rowley, Jon, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Royal, Walter, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Rubin, Lenard, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Rubin, Maury, 1991-2001 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Rubio, Salina, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Ruldolph, Kenny, Dec. 2002; various (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Rudolf, Keith, July 2005; various (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Rudolph, Peter, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Rudnick, Uwe, 1998; various (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Rueda, Astolfo, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Ruggerio, David, 1992-1997 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Ruiz, Philippe, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Rulli, Gary, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Rumbles, Melvin, Sept. 1993; various (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Rundell, Dan, undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Ruppe, Tony, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Rushing, Slade, undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Ruskell, Richard, Feb. 18, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Russell, Christian, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Russell, David, Aug. 31, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Russel, Jeffrey, 1998-2006 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Russo, Ian, 1996-2004 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Russodivito, Marcello, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Rutnya, Tom, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 35a)
  - Ryan, Thomas, 1994-2000 (Box 41, Folder 35b)
  - Saathoff, Lynn, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Saba, Andrew, May 17, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Sabin, Michael, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Sabo, Fred, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Sabon, Matthew, undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Sabore, Matthew, undated (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Sacchetti, Pierluigi, undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Sacchetto, Patrizio, April 1992 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Sachs, Dan, undated (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Sacramone, Rocco, Feb. 2008 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Sagaria, Sabato III, undated (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Saibi, Lotfi, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Sailhac, Alain, 1993-2005 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Saint-Denis, Pierre, Nov. 1993 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - De Saint Martin, Olivier, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Saja, Raymond, Sept. 5, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Sakatos, Jimmy, June 2006; various (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Salaway, Jeff, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Salazar, Cicely, undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Salcedo, Felix, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Saldana, Jorge, 1993-2003 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Sale, Paul, 1999-2006 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Salerni, Fabrizzo, 1997-2002 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Salih, Yahya, undated (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Salmon, Michael, 1992-2007 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Salomon, Xavier, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Salonia, Joseph, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Salonsky, Marc, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Salpetier, Frederic, Jan. 11, 2000; various (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Salter, Mark, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Salz, Kenji, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Sampanthavivat, Arun, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Sampiertro, Pepito, Sept. 21, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Samson, Marja, Nov. 1993; various (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Samson, Stephan, 1991-2002 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Samuelson, J.P., 1988-1992 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Samuelsson, Marcus (1 of 2), 1994-2005 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Samuelsson, Marcus (2 of 2), 1994-2005 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - Sanchez, Aaron, 2000-2006 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Sanchez, Abel, April 1994 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Sanchez, Pilar, 1997-2006 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Sand, Anne Kearney, May 19, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Sanderson, Kathleen, undated (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Sandoval, Patricio, 2004-2005 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Sandoval, Richard, 1997-2005 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Sanford, Jim, 1980-1983 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Sangiorgio, Rosario, June 20, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Santengelo, John, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Santacruz, Josefine, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Santibanez, Roberto, 1996-2004 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Santoro, Steve, 1993-2003 (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Santos, Carmen, 1997-2001 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Santos, Jason, 2003-2005 (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Santos, Ramiro, Jan. 16, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Sanzin, Johannes, 1996-2002 (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Sapienza, Mark, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Sappington, Adam, 2003-2008 (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - Saporito, Filippo, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Savalegui, Fernando, 1999-2004 (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - Savan, Suvir (1 of 2), undated (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - Savan, Suvir (2 of 2), 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - Sarci, Metin, undated (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - Sardi, Vincent, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - Sartory, Paul, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 99)
  - Sarvis, Shirley, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - Sasaki, Masaki, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 101)
  - Sassak, Curt, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 102)
  - Satchel, Orlando, 1996-2006 (Box 41, Folder 103)
  - Satkoff, Pricila, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 104)
  - Saudo, Jeff, undated (Box 41, Folder 105)
  - Saucy, Oliver, 1992-1998 (Box 41, Folder 106)
  - Sauton, Pascal, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 107)
  - Savage, Richard, 2003-2005 (Box 41, Folder 108)
  - Savok, Mark, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 109)
  - Savoy, Guy, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 110)
  - Saxer, Michael, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 111)
  - Saylor, Martin, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 112)
  - Sbraga, Kevin, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 113)
  - Scapin, Gianni, and Laura Penslero, 1992-2003 (Box 41, Folder 114)
  - Scala, Donna and Giovanni, 1995-2002 (Box 41, Folder 115)
  - Scalice, Joseph, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 116)
  - Scally, William and Melody, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 117)
  - Scamardella, Ralph, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 118)
  - Scanlon, Rebecca, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 119)
  - Scarduzio, Chris, 2000-2004 (Box 41, Folder 120)
  - Scargle, Victor, 2001-2004 (Box 41, Folder 121)
  - Schadler, Hans, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 122)
  - Schafer, Sarah, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 123)
  - Schafer, Tim, 1997-2001 (Box 41, Folder 124)
  - Schaedelin, Pierre, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 125)
  - Schaefer, John, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 126)
  - Schanley, Martin, undated (Box 41, Folder 127)
  - Schaudel, Tom, 1993-2007 (Box 41, Folder 128)
  - Schauffel, Craig and Kieth, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 129)
  - Schleehser, Brian, undated (Box 41, Folder 130)
  - Schehrer, Russell, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 131)
  - Scheib, Walter, 1994-2005 (Box 41, Folder 132)
  - Scheiman, Michael, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 133)